(Penny:)Hey, guys, don't forget,
my episode's on TV tomorrow night.
(Howard:)-We'll be there.
-Can we bring anything?
(Penny:)Oh, that's so sweet of you,
but I was gonna steal food from here.
(Penny:)You know, my treat.
(Sheldon:)Wait, if Howard's mother is coming,
then you should also steal marbles.
(Sheldon:)Because she's obese,
and hippos are obese,
(Sheldon:)and in the popular board game Hungry
Hungry Hippos, they eat marbles.
(Sheldon:)Maybe I need to dumb
these down for you.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard, do you think I'm funny?
-No.
(Leonard:)-Do you?
-I think I'm hysterical.
(Leonard:)I take it back.
That was funny.
(Sheldon:)The philosopher Henri Bergson
says it's funny
(Sheldon:)when a human being
behaves like an object.
(Leonard:)I bet that bit killed
at The Chuckle Hut.